site-analyzer.com 2019-04-17

# Website Analysis and SEO Tools | Site Analyzer

Site Analyzer («Company », « Website », « Site Analyzer »,or « We ») respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.  
Site Analyzer offers the service (the “Service”) to provide businesses and individuals with access to a rich collection of services related to search engine optimization, including search engine optimization tools and API. The Services include access to the website at www.site-analyzer.com. This privacy policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our Website and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

**This policy applies to information we collect:**  
\- On the Website  
\- In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and the Website  

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your only recourse is not to use our Website. By accessing or using the Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**  
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Site, including information:  
\- by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address ("personal information");  
\- that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as your company name; and/or about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our website and usage details.

**We collect this information:**  
\- Directly from you when you provide it to us.  
\- Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, email address, IP addresses and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

**Information You Provide to Us**  
The information we collect on or through our Website may include:  
\- Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes without limitation information provided at the time of subscribing to the Services, and when you report a problem with our Website.  
\- Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.  
\- Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.  
\- Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website 

**Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies**  
As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including without limitation:  
\- Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.  
\- Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

**The information we collect automatically is statistical data, and does not identify any individual. It helps us to improve our Sites and to deliver better and more personalized future services by enabling us to things such as:**  
\- Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.  
\- Speed up your searches.  
\- Recognize you when you return to our Website  
\- Provide better services in the future.

**The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:**  
**Cookies (or browser cookies)**. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Site.  
**Web Beacons**. Pages of our Site and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

**Service Providers**  
We may employ third party companies to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.  
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Google Analytics :**   
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

**FullStory**  
The FullStory Services utilize a powerful script that creates a new level of ease for website owners to understand the usability of their websites. Website owners who use FullStory Services can watch a DVR-like video playback of user sessions on their website, enabling meaningful insight into their users' experience, as an effective way to identify usability problems and other areas for improvement.  
For more information on the privacy practices of Fullstory, please visit the Fullstory privacy page: https://www.fullstory.com/legal/privacy/

We provide paid services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing.  
**The payment processors we work with is:**  
\- PayPal or Braintree. Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:  
\- To present our Website and its content to you.  
\- To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.  
\- To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.  
\- To provide you with notices about your subscriptions to the Service.  
\- To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.  
\- To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer.  
\- To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.  
\- In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.  
\- For any other purpose with your consent.

**We never sell your personal information or provide it to others for marketing purposes.**

**We may disclose your personal information:**  
\- To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.  
\- To enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.  
If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Site Analyzer, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**  
You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.  
You may also send us an e-mail at contact(at) site-analyzer(dot)com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us.  
Requests are treated within a maximum of one (1) month after receiving your complete request. In some cases, we cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

**Data Security**  
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.  
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.   
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Responsibility**  
The publisher makes his best to ensure the accessibility of the Website 24 hours a day and 7 days a week. However he will not in any way be held responsible for the unavailability of the Website for whatever reason.

**Website Publisher**  
VSI INNOVATION  
SAS with capital of 30.000€ (EUR)  
Whose head office is in VALENCIENNES, FRANCE (59300), 2, rue Péclet  
E-mail : contact (at) vsi-innovation (dot) com   
Intra-Community VAT : FR74 812 263 697  
SIREN : 812 263 697

The publishing manager is  
M. Tennessee VELDEMAN

The website hosting is ensured by VSI INNOVATION   
SAS with capital of 30.000€ (EUR)  
Whose head office is located in VALENCIENNES, FRANCE (59300), 2, rue Péclet  
Registered in the RCS of Valenciennes: n°812 263 697

Photos credits :  
VSI INNOVATION

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the primary e-mail address specified in your account and/or possibly through a notice on the Website home page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information**  
To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at contact(at)site-analyzer(dot)com.

**Last update:** 18th May 2018
